CASSANDRA PEREZ

GENIUS

CONTACT

(651) 373-1195 CASSANDRAENRIQ@ICLOUD.COM GITHUB CASSIEP94

PROFILE

Current student at the University Of Minnesota. I've spent the last five years in retail focused on deepening my understanding of technology. My unique professional experience stems from years of providing excellent customer support, creative problem solving and building customer loyalty.

SKILLS

- Javascript
- HTML, CSS
- Node JS
- React
- SQL

EXPERIENCE

APPLE

GENIUS | DEC 2019

- Update knowledge and skills to keep up with rapid advancements in computer technology.
- Answer user inquiries regarding computer software or hardware operation to resolve problems.

APPLE

TECHNICAL EXPERT| AUG 2018 - DEC 2019

- Troubleshoot, diagnose and perform repairs on iOS devices.
- Develop product knowledge and research required information using all available tools and resources.

SPECIALIST

APPLE | OCT 2016 - JAN 2018

- Drive sales, create owners, and build brand loyalty.
- Provide customized solutions based on each customer's specific needs including business, education and creative professionals.

EDUCATION

FULL STACK WEB-DEVELOPMENT CERTIFICATE
UNIVERSITY OF MINNESOTA | MARCH 2020 - SEPT 2020

LANGUAGES

SPANISH